Guide to the YourStory oral history project audio recordings 2005
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
YourStory oral history project audio recordings
2013
University of Utah Libraries, Special Collections Audio Visual Archives Special Collections 295 South 1500 East Salt Lake City, Utah 84112-0860 801-581-8864 http://www.lib.utah.edu/collections/multimedia-archives/
A0902
University of Utah
108 compact discs
The YourStory oral history project audio recordings (2005) consist of some of the first recordings made by the YourStory oral history project in an effort to collect the many and varied life stories of Utah residents. Although recordings in this collection date from February-June 2005 only, YourStory is an ongoing progam "supported by the Documentary Studies program in the College of Humanities at the University of Utah" and "designed to facilitate the recording of interviews with relatives and friends, and to help individuals provide a lasting legacy of their own stories for families and loved ones."
Historical Note
YourStory was founded in 2004 by Professor Meg Brady of the Department of English and the Ethnic Studies Program at the University of Utah. The project is an effort to record the life stories of all Utahns. YourStory has recording studios across the Wasatch Front, including the Chase Home Museum of Folk Art in Liberty Park and the Huntsman Cancer Institute and offers its services to "every Utahn, no matter how ordinary, [who] has a story to tell."
The YourStory oral history project audio recordings (2005) consist of some of the first recordings made by the YourStory oral history project in an effort to collect the many and varied life stories of Utah residents. Although YourStory is an ongoing project, materials in this collectin date from February-June 2005 only. All materials are digital and available to listen to on compact disc.
Collection is arranged in chronological order.
Materials must be used on-site; no use of original material, access copies will be made available for viewing. Five business days advanced notice required. Access to parts of this collection may be restricted under provisions of state or federal law, condition of the material, or by donor.
Utah; Oral history; City and Town Life; Home and Family; Sound Recordings; Oral Histories; Sound recordings
- Paul Lenhart interviewed by Nyssa Densley, 2005 February 3; Compact disc (Disc 1)
- Thomas O. Tipps and Robert N. Tipps interviewed by Meg Brady, Betsy Tipps also present, 2005 February 5; Compact disc (Disc 2)
- Thomas O. Tipps and Robert N. Tipps interviewed by Meg Brady, Betsy Tipps also present (2), 2005 February 5; Compact disc (Disc 3)
- Charles Eubank Sr. interviewed by Meg Brady, 2005 February 6; Compact disc (Disc 4)
- Charles Eubank Sr. interviewed by Meg Brady (2), 2005 February 6; Compact disc (Disc 5)
- Betty Clark Ruff interviewed by Edie Kochenour, 2005 February 8; Compact disc (Disc 6)
- Hannah Pearl Wilding interviewed by Edie Kochenour, 2005 February 8; Compact disc (Disc 7)
- Dewaine H. Ewell interviewed by Jenny Jones, 2005 February 9; Compact disc (Disc 8)
- Cherle B. Ewell interviewed by Jenny Jones, 2005 February 9; Compact disc (Disc 9)
- George A. Phelps interviewed by Jenny Jones, 2005 February 9; Compact disc (Disc 10)
- Dortha Nelson Rasband interviewed by Nyssa Densley, 2005 February 10; Compact disc (Disc 11)
- Marjorie Scott Sears Regnier interviewed by Nyssa Densley, 2005 February 10; Compact disc (Disc 12)
- Ruth H. Rampton interviewed by Laura Gee; Eunice Gabor, McKinley McMiller, and Kathie McMillen also present, 2005 February 11; Compact disc (Disc 13)
- Leonard V. Todd interviewed by Laura Gee, 2005 February 11; Compact disc (Disc 14)
- David W. Lyon interviewed by Edie Kochenour, 2005 February 15; Compact disc (Disc 15)
- Janice Cameron interviewed by Edie Kochenour, 2005 February 15; Compact disc (Disc 16)
- Ralph M. Tannenbaum interviewed by Edie Kochenour, 2005 February 15; Compact disc (Disc 17)
- Helen Wright and Emma Linschoten interviewed by Jenny Jones, 2005 February 16; Compact disc (Disc 18)
- Helen Wright and Emma Linschoten interviewed by Jenny Jones (2), 2005 February 16; Compact disc (Disc 19)
- Claudia A. Howard interviewed by Jenny Jones, 2005 February 16; Compact disc (Disc 20)
- George A. Phelps interviewed by Jenny Jones, 2005 February 16; Compact disc (Disc 21)
- Paul Lenhart interviewed by Nyssa Densley, 2005 February 10; Compact disc (Disc 22)
- Paul Lenhart interviewed by Nyssa Densley (2), 2005 February 17; Compact disc (Disc 23)
- Stuart Jardine interviewed by Meg Brady, 2005 February 17; Compact disc (Disc 24)
- Winnifred Jardine interviewed by Meg Brady, 2005 February 17; Compact disc (Disc 25)
- Teresa L. Cronin interviewed by Laura Gee, 2005 February 18; Compact disc (Disc 26)
- Thelma Vermillion interviewed by Laura Gee, 2005 February 18; Compact disc (Disc 27)
- Virginia M. Nielsen interviewed by Laura Gee, Ron Mertenson also present, 2005 February 18; Compact disc (Disc 28)
- Lynette Yerbury interviewed by Meg Brady, 2005 February 19; Compact disc (Disc 29)
- Lorraine Mayne interviewed by Meg Brady, 2005 February 19; Compact disc (Disc 30)
- Mary Cummings Shootman interviewed by Meg Brady, 2005 February 20; Compact disc (Disc 31)
- Gregory J. Skedros interviewed by Meg Brady (Greeks), 2005 February 20; Compact disc (Disc 32)
- John A. Chipian interviewed by Meg Brady (Greeks), 2005 February 23; Compact disc (Disc 33)
- George Pappas interviewed by Meg Brady (Greeks), 2005 February 23; Compact disc (Disc 34)
- George Pappas interviewed by Meg Brady (Greeks) (2), 2005 February 23; Compact disc (Disc 34)
- Paul Lenhart interviewed by Nyssa Densley, 2005 February 24; Compact disc (Disc 35)
- John S. Smith interviewed by Laura Gee, ReNee Call also present, 2005 February 26; Compact disc (Disc 36)
- Donald C. Griffin interviewed by Laura Gee, 2005 February 26; Compact disc (Disc 37)
- Annette Alberico Cobbley interviewed by Meg Brady, 2005 February 28; Compact disc (Disc 38)
- Annette Alberico Cobbley interviewed by Meg Brady (2), 2005 February 28; Compact disc (Disc 39)
- Betty Evenson interviewed by Edie Kochenour, 2005 March 1; Compact disc (Disc 40)
- Charles R. Brown interviewed by Edie Kochenour, 2005 March 1; Compact disc (Disc 41)
- David W. Lyon interviewed by Edie Kochenour, 2005 March 1; Compact disc (Disc 42)
- Chris Metos interviewed by Meg Brady (Greeks), 2005 March 3; Compact disc (Disc 43)
- Gary Bates interviewed by Nyssa Densley, 2005 March 3; Compact disc (Disc 44)
- Jenne E. Winzeler and Robert G. Winzeler interviewed by Laura Gee; Larry Winzeler, Cheri Winzeler, and Jane Smith also present, 2005 March 4; Compact disc (Disc 45)
- Jenne E. Winzeler and Robert G. Winzeler interviewed by Laura Gee; Larry Winzeler, Cheri Winzeler, and Jane Smith also present (2), 2005 March 4; Compact disc (Disc 46)
- Raymond S. Fletcher interviewed by Nyssa Densley, 2005 February 24; Compact disc (Disc 47)
- Janice Cameron interviewed by Edie Kochenour, 2005 March 8; Compact disc (Disc 48)
- Lenora Snarr interviewed by Laura Gee, Joan Blank also present, 2005 March 11; Compact disc (Disc 49)
- Carol Edic interviewed by Edie Kochenour, 2005 March 15; Compact disc (Disc 50)
- Carol Edic interviewed by Edie Kochenour (2), 2005 March 15; Compact disc (Disc 51)
- Wilbert D. Carlson interviewed by Jenny Jones, 2005 March 16; Compact disc (Disc 52)
- Joan Carlson interviewed by Jenny Jones, 2005 March 16; Compact disc (Disc 53)
- John S. Smith interviewed by Jenny Jones, 2005 March 16; Compact disc (Disc 54)
- Bessie K. Markos interviewed by Meg Brady (Greeks), 2005 March 17; Compact disc (Disc 55)
- Bessie K. Markos interviewed by Meg Brady (Greeks) (2), 2005 March 17; Compact disc (Disc 56)
- Chris Metos interviewed by Meg Brady (Greeks), 2005 March 18; Compact disc (Disc 57)
- Mark F. Everett interviewed by Carol Louder, 2005 March 19; Compact disc (Disc 58)
- Betty Evenson interviewed by Edie Kochenour, 2005 March 22; Compact disc (Disc 59)
- David W. Lyon interviewed by Edie Kochenour, 2005 March 22; Compact disc (Disc 60)
- John S. Smith interviewed by Jenny Jones, 2005 March 23; Compact disc (Disc 61)
- Janice Cameron interviewed by Jenny Jones, 2005 March 23; Compact disc (Disc 62)
- Janice Cameron interviewed by Jenny Jones (2), 2005 March 23; Compact disc (Disc 63)
- Barbara Griffin, Georgia Demarco interviewed by Laura Gee, 2005 March 25; Compact disc (Disc 64)
- Barbara Griffin, Georgia Demarco interviewed by Laura Gee, 2005 March 25; Compact disc (Disc 65)
- Susan Whitney interviewed by Laura Gee; Betty Bernick, Frances Cockrill, and Ann Mortland also present, 2005 March 25; Compact disc (Disc 66)
- Dorothy Sweitzer interviewed by Meg Brady, 2005 March 26; Compact disc (Disc 67)
- Ellen N. Webb interviewed by Meg Brady, 2005 March 26; Compact disc (Disc 68)
- Leon A. Walters interviewed by Edie Kochenour, 2005 March 29; Compact disc (Disc 69)
- Leon A. Walters interviewed by Edie Kochenour (2), 2005 March 29; Compact disc (Disc 70)
- Margaret Earl interviewed by Meg Brady, 2005 March 31; Compact disc (Disc 71)
- Robert J. Sheridan interviewed by Meg Brady, 2005 April 4; Compact disc (Disc 72)
- Robert J. Sheridan interviewed by Meg Brady (2), 2005 April 4; Compact disc (Disc 73)
- Susan Klinker Czop interviewed by Laura Gee, 2005 April 8; Compact disc (Disc 74)
- Richard Stephens interviewed by Laura Gee, 2005 April 8; Compact disc (Disc 75)
- Mark F. Everett interviewed by Carol Louder, 2005 April 9; Compact disc (Disc 76)
- Mark F. Everett interviewed by Carol Louder (2), 2005 April 9; Compact disc (Disc 77)
- Kojo Essah Ampiah-Davis interviewed by Carol Louder, 2005 April 9; Compact disc (Disc 78)
- Ronald V. Belnap interviewed by Jenny Jones, 2005 April 13; Compact disc (Disc 79)
- Inge Bates interviewed by Nyssa Densley, 2005 April 14; Compact disc (Disc 80)
- Nick P. Sefakis interviewed by Nyssa Densley (Greeks), 2005 April 14; Compact disc (Disc 81)
- Nick P. Sefakis interviewed by Nyssa Densley (Greeks) (2), 2005 April 14; Compact disc (Disc 82)
- Peter Vrontikis interviewed by Nyssa Densley (Greeks), 2005 April 14; Compact disc (Disc 83)
- Alison M. Larsen interviewed by Laura Gee, 2005 April 15; Compact disc (Disc 84)
- Susan Klinker Czop interviewed by Laura Gee, 2005 April 15; Compact disc (Disc 85)
- Nick P. Sefakis interviewed by Nyssa Densley (Greeks), 2005 April 21; Compact disc (Disc 86)
- Gary Bates interviewed by Nyssa Densley, 2005 April 21; Compact disc (Disc 87)
- Corinne Lavin interviewed by Edie Kochenour, 2005 April 26; Compact disc (Disc 88)
- Inge Bates interviewed by Nyssa Densley, 2005 May 5; Compact disc (Disc 89)
- Joseph J. Czop interviewed by Carol Louder, 2005 May 6; Compact disc (Disc 90)
- Laurie Czop interviewed by Carol Louder, 2005 May 6; Compact disc (Disc 91)
- Sarah Seamons Daines interviewed by Edie Kochenour, 2005 May 10; Compact disc (Disc 92)
- Robert K. Stanger interviewed by Jenny Jones, 2005 June 7; Compact disc (Disc 93)
- Janice Cameron interviewed by Jenny Jones, 2005 June 7; Compact disc (Disc 94)
- Amos A. Jordan interviewed by Jenny Jones, Linda Mabey also present, 2005 June 8; Compact disc (Disc 95)
- Amos A. Jordan interviewed by Jenny Jones, Linda Mabey also present (2), 2005 June 8; Compact disc (Disc 96)
- Ladell Richardson interviewed by Nyssa Densley, 2005 June 9; Compact disc (Disc 97)
- Betty Glenn Richardson interviewed by Nyssa Densley, 2005 June 9; Compact disc (Disc 98)
- Dorothy M. Mickelsen interviewed by Meg Brady, 2005 June 11; Compact disc (Disc 99)
- Dorothy M. Mickelsen interviewed by Meg Brady, 2005 June 11; Compact disc (Disc 100)
- Dorothy M. Mickelsen interviewed by Meg Brady (2), 2005 June 11; Compact disc (Disc 101)
- Raymond S. Fletcher interviewed by Meg Brady, 2005 June 14; Compact disc (Disc 102)
- Raymond S. Fletcher interviewed by Meg Brady (2), 2005 June 14; Compact disc (Disc 103)
- Helen Bezzant and Betty Evenson interviewed by Jenny Jones, 2005 June 14; Compact disc (Disc 104)
- Helen Bezzant and Betty Evenson interviewed by Jenny Jones (2), 2005 June 14; Compact disc (Disc 105)
- Don R. Merrill interviewed by Rachel Marston, 2005 June 15; Compact disc (Disc 106)
- Joan Bird Merrill interviewed by Rachel Marston, 2005 June 15; Compact disc (Disc 107)
- Heber Lacelle Haymond interviewed by Nyssa Densley, 2005 June 16; Compact disc (Disc 108)